William Edgar Borah Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Land Utilization File, 1909-1935 (Box 529-581)
  - 1920-1921
    - Miscellaneous
    - National parks
    - Reclamation
      - Black Canyon, Idaho
      - Boise, Idaho, project
      - Bruneau, Idaho, project
      - Fall River, Idaho, project
      - General
      - Proposed projects
    - Roads
    - Soldiers and sailors settlements
    - Town sites matters
    - Washington Water Power Co.
  - 1921-1922 (Box 553)
    - Alaskan matters
    - American Falls, Idaho, contract
    - Bird refuge
    - Carey lands
    - Claims
    - Desert entries
    - Drainage
    - Forest reserves
      - General
      - H.R. 77, (2 folders)
    - Grazing permits (Box 554)
    - Homesteads
      - Enlarged
      - Forest reserve
      - General, A-Z, (2 folders)
      - Stockraising
    - Indian lands
    - Irrigation districts
    - Mines and mining
    - Miscellaneous
    - National parks
    - Reclamation (Box 555)
      - Black Canyon, Idaho
      - Boise, Idaho, project
      - Columbia Basin project
      - Dubois, Idaho, project
      - Extension of payments, (2 folders)
      - General
      - Minidoka, Idaho, project
      - Proposed project
    - Roads
    - Smith-McNary bill (Box 556)
    - State lands, exchange
    - Town site matters
  - 1922-1923
    - American Falls contract
    - Bird refuge
    - Carey lands
    - Claims
    - Contests
    - Desert entries
    - Drainage
    - Forest reserves
    - Grazing permits
    - Homesteads
      - Enlarged
      - Forest reserve
      - General, A-Z, (2 folders)
      - Stockraising
    - Indian lands
    - Irrigation districts (Box 557)
    - Miscellaneous
    - National parks
    - Reclamation
      - Boise, Idaho, project
      - Boise-Mora, Idaho, project
      - Columbia Basin project
      - Extension of payments, A-Z, (3 folders)
      - General (Box 558)
      - King Hill, Idaho, project
    - Reservoir
    - Roads
    - Script
    - Smith-McNary bill
    - State lands, exchange
    - Timber and stone claims
    - Washington Water Power Co.
  - 1923-1924
    - American Falls, Idaho, contract
    - Claims
    - Desert entries
    - Drainage
    - Forest reserves
    - Grazing permits, (2 folders) (Box 559)
    - Homesteads
      - Enlarged
      - Forest reserve
      - General, A-W, (2 folders)
      - Stockraising
    - Indian lands
    - Irrigation districts
    - Mines and mining
    - Miscellaneous (Box 560)
    - National parks
    - Oil and gas leases
    - Reclamation
      - Black Canyon, Idaho
      - Boise, Idaho, project
      - Boise-Mora, Idaho, project
      - Dubois project
      - Extension of payments, B-W, (2 folders)
      - Fort Hall, Idaho, project
    - Reclamation
      - General
      - Hillcrest, Idaho, project (Box 561)
      - King Hill, Idaho, project
      - Minidoka, Idaho, project
      - Owyhee, Idaho, project
      - Payette Lakes, Idaho
      - Relief bill
      - Smith bill
    - Reservoirs
    - Roads, (2 folders)
    - Roads, Arkansas
    - Sale of certain lands
    - Timber and stone claims
  - 1924-1925
    - American Falls, Idaho, contract
    - Bridges
    - Claims
    - Desert entries
    - Drainage
    - Forest reserves (Box 562)
    - Gas and oil leases
    - Grazing permits
    - Homesteads
      - Enlarged
      - General, B-T, (2 folders)
      - Stockraising
    - Indian lands
    - Irrigation districts
    - Land offices
    - Mineral lands
    - Mines and mining
    - Miscellaneous
    - Reclamation (Box 563)
      - Black Canyon, Idaho
      - Boise, Idaho, project
      - Boise-Mora, Idaho, project
      - Columbia Basin project
      - Dubois, Idaho, project
      - Extension of payments, A-Y, (2 folders)
      - Fort Hall, Idaho, project
      - General
      - Hillcrest, Idaho, project
      - King Hill, Idaho, project
      - Minidoka, Idaho, project
      - Nampa-Meridian, Idaho, project
      - Owyhee, Idaho, project
      - Relief bill
    - Reservoirs
    - Roads
    - Roads, Arkansas
    - Sales of certain lands
    - Surveys
  - 1925-1926 (Box 564)
    - American Falls, Idaho, contract
    - Bridges
    - Claims
    - Desert entries
    - Forest fire prevention
    - Forest reserves
    - Gas and oil leases
    - Grazing permits
    - Homesteads
      - General
        - C-Z, (3 folders)
        - Lundquist and Kildee
        - Nantz, Frank L.
      - Stockraising (Box 565)
    - Indian lands
    - Irrigation districts
    - Land offices
    - Mines and mining
    - Mining lands
    - Miscellaneous
    - Parks
    - Reclamation
      - Black Canyon, Idaho
      - Boise, Idaho, project
      - Boise-Mora, Idaho, project
      - Columbia Basin project
      - Dubois, Idaho, project
      - Extension of payments, A-T
      - Fort Hall, Idaho. project
      - General, (2 folders)
      - Hillcrest, Idaho project
      - Jones bill (Box 566)
      - Minidoka., Idaho, project
      - Owyhee, Idaho, project
    - Reservoirs
    - Roads, (2 folders)
    - Scrip
    - Stanfield bill (S. 2584)
    - State lands, exchange
    - Surveys
    - Timber and stone claims
    - Utah oil matters
  - 1927
    - American Falls, Idaho, project
    - Bridges
    - Claims
    - Desert entries
    - Drainage (Box 567)
    - Forest reserves
    - Gas and oil leases
    - Grazing permits
    - Homesteads
      - General
        - H-R, (2 folders)
        - Holden, W. N., Ethel and Nellie
        - Lundquist and Kildee
      - Stockraising
    - Indian lands, (2 folders)
    - Irrigation district
    - Land offices (Box 568)
    - Mines and mining
    - Miscellaneous
    - National parks
    - Reclamation
      - Black Canyon, Idaho
      - Boise, Idaho, project
      - Boulder Dam
      - Fort Hall, Idaho, project
      - Columbia Basin project
      - General
      - Hillcrest, Idaho, project
      - Minidoka, Idaho, project
    - Reservoirs
    - Roads
    - Surveys
    - Yellowstone Reservoir site
  - 1927-1928 (Box 569)
    - American Falls, Idaho, project
    - Boulder Dam
    - Claims
    - Conflict of reclamation projects
    - Desert entries
    - Forest reserves
    - Grazing permits
    - Homesteads
      - General, A-Z
      - Stockraising
    - Indian lands
    - Irrigation districts
    - Marshes
    - Minidoka, Idaho, project
    - Mineral lands
    - Mines and mining (Box 570)
    - Mining claims
    - Miscellaneous
    - National parks
    - Oil and gas leases
    - Reclamation
      - Black Canyon, Idaho
      - Boise, Idaho, project
      - Columbia Basin project
      - Fort Hall, Idaho, project
      - General
      - Hillcrest, Idaho, project
      - Minidoka, Idaho, project
    - Reservoirs
    - Roads
    - State lands, exchange (Box 571)
    - Surveys
    - Timber and stone claims
  - 1928-1929
    - Boulder Dam
    - Carey lands
    - Claims
    - Drainage
    - Forest fire prevention
    - Forest reserves, (4 folders)
    - Fort Hall, Idaho, project (Box 572)
    - Grazing permits
    - Homesteads
      - General, B-W, (2 folders)
      - Lundquist and Kildee
    - Idaho Power Co.
    - Indian lands
    - Inland waterways
    - Irrigation districts
    - Mines and mining
    - Mining claims
    - Miscellaneous
    - Oil and gas leases (Box 573)
    - Reclamation
      - Black Canyon, Idaho
      - General
      - King Hill, Idaho, project
      - Minidoka, Idaho, project
      - Owyhee, Idaho, project
    - Reservoirs
    - Roads
    - Sale of timber
    - State lands, exchange
    - Surveys
    - Transfer of public lands
    - Waterways
  - 1929-1931
    - American Falls, Idaho
      - Contract
      - Project
    - Bonds, Idaho land
    - Boulder Dam
    - Bridges (Box 574)
    - Carey lands
    - Claims
    - Desert entries
    - Drainage
    - Forest fire prevention
    - Forest reserves, (2 folders)
    - Fort Hall, Idaho, project
    - Grazing permits, (2 folders)
    - Homesteads (Box 575)
      - General
        - A-W, (5 folders)
        - Strickland, George W.
      - Stockraising
    - Indian land
    - Inland waterways
    - Irrigation districts
    - Mineral lands (Box 576)
    - Mines and mining
    - Miscellaneous
    - National parks
    - Oil and gas leases, (2 folders)
    - Reclamation
      - Black Canyon, Idaho
      - Boise, Idaho, project
      - Columbia Basin project
      - Extension of payment
      - General
      - Hillcrest, Idaho, project
      - Minidoka, Idaho, project
      - Owyhee, Idaho, project
    - Reservoirs
    - Rivers and harbors
    - Roads, (1 folder) (Box 577)
    - Sales of lots
    - Surveys
  - 1931-1932
    - American Falls, Idaho, project
    - Assay office
    - Bridges, (2 folders)
    - Claims
    - Desert entries
    - Drainage
    - Forest fire prevention
    - Forest reserves (2 folders
    - Fort Hall, Idaho,. project
    - Grazing permits (Box 578)
    - Homesteads
      - General, B-Y
      - Stockraising
    - Indian lands
    - Irrigation districts
    - Land office
    - Mines and mining, (3 folders)
    - Miscellaneous
    - National parks
    - Oil and gas leases
    - Reclamation
      - Black Canyon, Idaho
      - Boise, Idaho, project
      - Extention of payments
      - General
      - King Hall, Idaho, project
      - Owyhee, Idaho, project
    - Reservoirs
    - Roads (Box 579)
    - Surveys
    - Timber lands, exchange
  - 1932-1934
    - American Falls, Idaho. project
    - Carey lands
    - Claims
    - Desert entries
    - Drainage
    - Forest fire prevention
    - Forest reserves, (3 folders)
    - Forest services (Box 580)
    - Grazing permits
    - Homesteads
      - General
      - Stockraising
    - Indian affairs
    - Indian lands
    - Irrigation districts
    - Land office
    - Mines and mining, (3 folders)
    - Mining claims (Box 581)
    - Miscellaneous
    - National parks
    - Oil and gas leases
    - Reclamation
      - Boise, Idaho, project
      - Clark Fork River
      - Extension of payments
      - General
      - Miscellaneous
      - Owyhee, Idaho, project
      - Proposed projects
      - Salmon River
    - Rivers and harbors
    - Roads
    - Surveys
    - Timber lands, exchange
  - 1934-1935, irrigation districts
- Patronage File, 1908-1940 (Box 582-598)
  Letters received and carbons of letters sent. Subdivided initially into Post Office patronage and patronage concerning other government agencies and government positions.
  The Post Office material is concerned mostly with patronage in Idaho and arranged alphabetically by name of person. The material relating to other government agencies and positions is arranged alphabetically by name of position or agency.
  - Post Office Department (Box 582)
    - Idaho (by county and town)
      - Albion-Boise, 1910, (6 folders)
      - Boise, 199-Buhl, (6 folders) (Box 583)
      - Buick-Crystal, (8 folders) (Box 584)
      - Culdesac-Golden Age Mine, (11 folders) (Box 585)
      - Gooding-Idaho Falls, (8 folders) (Box 586)
      - Ilo-Lowman, (9 folders) (Box 587)
      - Mackay-Moulton, (10 folders) (Box 588)
      - Mountainhome-Orofino, (9 folders) (Box 589)
      - Oxford-Riddle, (9 folders) (Box 590)
      - Rigby-Stafford, (11 folders) (Box 591)
      - Stanley-Weippe, (9 folders) (Box 592)
      - Weiser-Yellow Pine, (5 folders) (Box 593)
    - Other states, A-W, (3 folders)
    - Various Government agencies and positions (Box 594)
      - Alaskan appointments
      - Assayer
        - Assistant to attorney general
        - Board of Appraiser, New York
        - Circuit Court of Appeals
        - Conciliation Division, Labor Department
        - Consul to Sweden
        - Consular positions
        - Diplomatic corps
      - District Attorney
      - Examiner, Fort Hall Agency (National Bank)
      - Examiner
        - National Bank
        - State Bank
      - Federal Farm Loan Board
      - Federal judgeship, Idaho
      - Federal Land Bank
      - Federal Reserve Board
      - General Land Office
        - Indian Affairs Commissioners
        - Indian Inspector
      - Interior Department (Box 595)
      - Internal Revenue
      - Internal Revenue Collector
      - Interstate Commerce Commissioner
      - Labor Board, mail service
      - Land Office, Idaho
        - Blackfoot-Coeur D'Alene
        - Boise (Box 596)
        - Hailey-Sinclair, Bartlett, (2 folders)
      - Marshall, U.S., (2 folders)
      - Memorandum of agreement
      - Military Bureau, Chief of
      - Minister to (Box 597)
        - China
        - Spain
      - Prohibition agents, (2 folders)
      - Surveyor General
      - War Finance Corp.
      - Miscellaneous
        - A-H, (3 folders)
        - J-W, (4 folders) (Box 598)
        - Evans, Evan
- Pension File (Box 599-628)
  Arranged alphabetically by name of individual and therein chronologically.
  - Abbott, Minnie C-Badger, J.W. (Box 599)
  - Badley, Durbin L.-Berryman, Charles H. (Box 600)
  - Biggerstaff, Eric S.-Broomfield, D.P. (Box 601)
  - Brown, Ella-Chapman, Guy E. (Box 602)
  - Chase, George E.-Connely, Leroy G. (Box 603)
  - Connors, John C.-Dana, Joseph C. (Box 604)
  - Danford, Marcia-Duggins, Williams (Box 605)
  - Duncan, Thomas-Felton, Chester H. (Box 606)
  - Finegan, John-Garretson, J.M. (Box 607)
  - Garrett, Henry-Greene, James D. (Box 608)
  - Greenley, Haggie-Harris, William H. (Box 609)
  - Harrison, Mary-Hutt, Ida (Box 610)
  - Hoag, Wilson-Hussey, Wilbern (Box 611)
  - Hutson, Joseph W.-Jones, Stephen D. (Box 612)
  - Jordan, James, Jr.-Laymon, Elmer (Box 613)
  - Leach, Laura F.-Lyon, Taylor C. (Box 614)
  - MacDonald, Archie-Manning, Susan E. (Box 615)
  - Maringer, Elizabeth-Moon, John W. (Box 616)
  - Moore, Aaron-Owen, William H. (Box 617)
  - Pachwood, M.F.-Pierce, S.N. (Box 618)
  - Pierson, John A.-Reel, Hiram F. (Box 619)
  - Reeve, Eliza A.-Rogers, Mary E. (Box 620)
  - Roming, Nellie-Schnaitmann, C.H. (Box 621)
  - Schollars, Aaron-Smith, Alwilda (Box 622)
  - Smith, Andrew W.-Stewart, Andrew J. (Box 623)
  - Stewart, Carrie-Thomas, John E. (Box 624)
  - Thomas, Jonathan-Wallace, William J. (Box 625)
  - Walling, N.-White, Calvin R. (Box 626)
  - White, Charles F.-Wilson, Malinda (Box 627)
  - Wilson, Rettie-Zufall, Alice (Box 628)
- Veterans Claims File (Box 629-660)
  Arranged alphabetically by name of person and therein chronologically. Veterans claims filed under War Risk Insurance are separated and arranged by regional office.
  - Abbott, Albert F.-Askew, George W. (Box 629)
  - Atha, Clement-Beason, Myrl (Box 630)
  - Beck, Edward V.-Borup, Harry (Box 631)
  - Boswell, Chester A.-Brundage, Evelyn (Box 632)
  - Buchanan, David-Byrne, George (Box 633)
  - Cage, Milton-Clark, William (Box 634)
  - Clary, John-Cyr, Clifford (Box 635)
  - Dahlberg, Robert-Dial, Norman (Box 636)
  - Dickens, Guy-Faust, Theodore (Box 637)
  - Fenn, Frank A.-Gardner, Daniel (Box 638)
  - Garvin, Arthur-Greseck, J.A. (Box 639)
  - Gribble, James E.-Harmon, William (Box 640)
  - Harner, David-Holsclaw, Dugald S. (Box 641)
  - Hoover, Florence-Johanson, Johan (Box 642)
  - John, James E.-Kvles, W.L. (Box 643)
  - Lafferty, T. F.-Martin, Martin (Box 644)
  - Mary, Frank E.-Meister, William A. (Box 645)
  - Mendenhall, Francis-Mills, Christopher (Box 646)
  - Miscellaneous
    - A-S
    - T-Y (Box 647)
  - O'Rorke, Bartley C.-Moers, August
  - Osthaus, Goodin P.-Peterson, James N. (Box 648)
  - Pettyjohn, Charles-Reed, Charles H. (Box 649)
  - Reese, Jefferson-Routson, Leonard (Box 650)
  - Rowe, Frank-Simpson, William (Box 651)
  - Skowronck, Joseph-Sutton, John (Box 652)
  - Swank, Clay-Volters, Edward (Box 653)
  - Wallace, L. A.-Wolfe, Gerald (Box 654)
  - Walter, William R-Ziebarth, John A. (Box 655)
  - Regional office (Box 656)
    - Boise, Idaho
    - Chicago, Ill.
    - Cincinnati, Ohio
    - Denver, Colo.
    - Los Angeles, Calif.
    - New Orleans, La.
    - Phoenix, Ariz.
    - Portland, Oreg.
    - San Francisco, Calif.
    - Washington, D.C.
    - Miscellaneous, (1 folder) (Box 657)
  - War risk insurance (Box 658)
    - Allen, Henry A.-Guymon, Vernon
    - Hallihan, Bernard-Norris, Carl (Box 659)
    - O'Donnell, Colin-Zirbel, Henry B. (Box 660)
- Public Opinion File, 1925-1939 (Box 661-753)
  - Neutrality, 1939 (Box 661)
    - Jan.-Mar.
    - Mar.-Apr. (Box 662)
    - Apr. (Box 663)
    - May-June (Box 664)
    - June-July (Box 665)
    - July (Box 666)
    - July-Sept. (Box 667)
    - Sept. 1-12 (Box 668)
    - Sept. 12-13 (Box 669)
    - Sept. 13-14 (Box 670)
    - Sept. 14 (Box 671)
    - Sept. 14-15 (Box 672)
    - Sept. 15 (Box 673)
    - Sept. 15 (Box 674)
    - Sept. 15 (Box 675)
    - Sept. 15-16 (Box 676)
    - Sept. 16 (Box 677)
    - Sept. 16-17 (Box 678)
    - Sept. 17-18 (Box 679)
    - Sept. 17-18 (Box 680)
    - Sept. 17–18 (Box 681)
    - Sept. 17-18 (Box 682)
    - Sept. 18-19 (Box 683)
    - Sept. 19 (Box 684)
    - Sept.19 (Box 685)
    - Sept. 19-20 (Box 686)
    - Sept. 19-20 (Box 687)
    - Sept. 20-21 (Box 688)
    - Sept. 21-22 (Box 689)
    - Sept. 22-23 (Box 690)
    - Sept. 23-24 (Box 691)
    - Sept. 24-25 (Box 692)
    - Sept. 25-26 (Box 693)
    - Sept. 26-28 (Box 694)
    - Sept. 28-30 (Box 695)
    - Sept., no dates
    - Sept., no dates-Oct. 2 (Box 696)
    - Sept., no dates-Oct. 2 (Box 697)
    - Sept., no dates-Oct. 2 (Box 698)
    - Sept., no dates-Oct. 2 (Box 699)
    - Oct. 2-3 (Box 700)
    - Oct. 4-7 (Box 701)
    - Oct. 8-10 (Box 702)
    - Oct. 11-18 (Box 703)
    - Oct. 19-23 (Box 704)
    - Oct. 24-30; Oct. no dates (Box 705)
    - Oct., no dates-Dec. (Box 706)
    - Telegrams for Borah (Box 707)
      - Sept. 1-18
      - Sept. 19-Oct. 27 (Box 708)
    - Correspondence against Borah (Box 709)
      - Aug. 6-Sept. 15
      - Sept. 16-22 (Box 710)
      - Sept. 23-30 (Box 711)
      - Sept., no dates
      - Oct.-Nov. (Box 712)
    - Postcards for Borah (Box 713)
      - May-Sept.
      - Sept. (Box 714)
      - Sept. (Box 715)
      - Sept.-Oct. (Box 716)
      - Sept.-Oct. (Box 717)
    - Postcards against Borah, Sept.-Oct. (Box 718)
  - Spanish embargo, 1938-1939 (Box 719)
    - Apr. 14-24
    - Apr. 25-May 18 (Box 720)
    - May 18-Dec. (Box 721)
    - Jan.-Feb. 13, 1939 (Box 722)
    - Feb. 14-16 (Box 723)
    - Feb. 17-24 (Box 724)
    - Feb. 24-25 (Box 725)
    - Feb. 26-Mar. 17 (Box 726)
    - Postcards (Box 727)
      - Apr.-May 1938
      - May 1938 (Box 728)
      - Jan.-Feb. 16, 1939 (Box 729)
      - Feb. 17-20 (Box 730)
      - Feb. 22-28 (Box 731)
      - Feb. 28-Mar. 6, 1939 (Box 732)
  - Supreme Court reorganization, 1937 (Box 733)
    - Jan.-Feb. 7
    - Feb. 8-10 (Box 734)
    - Feb. 11-15 (Box 735)
    - Feb. 15-18 (Box 736)
    - Feb. 19-23 (Box 737)
    - Feb. 24-28, and no dates (Box 738)
    - Mar. 1-8 (Box 739)
    - Mar. 9-12 (Box 740)
    - Mar. 12-19 (Box 741)
    - Mar. 20-31, and no dates (Box 742)
    - Apr. 1-May 15 (Box 743)
    - May 17-June 22 (Box 744)
    - June 23-July 8 (Box 745)
    - July 9-18 (Box 746)
    - July 18-Aug. (Box 747)
  - World Court, 1925-1926 (Box 748)
    - Mar.-Dec. 15, 1925
    - Dec. 16, 1925-Jan. 1926 (Box 749)
  - Works Progress Administration, 1939 (Box 750)
  - Republican party reorganization, 1934 (Box 751)
  - National Recovery Administration codes (Box 752)
    - Jan.-Feb 1934
    - Feb.-May 1935 (Box 753)
- Subject File, 1905-1940 (Box 754-778)
  Letters received and carbons of letters sent, newspaper clippings, memoranda, statements, printed matter.
  Arranged alphabetically by subject and therein chronologically.
  - Alien actors' immigration, 1938 (Box 754)
  - Antitrust laws, repeal of. Jan. 18-24, 1934, (3 folders)
  - Bill of Landing Treaty, Dec. 1927-Mar. 1928
  - Black, Hugo LaFayette, nomination to Supreme Court
    - Mar.-Aug. 14, 1937
    - Aug. 15-18, 1937, undated (Box 755)
  - Bootleg liquor, Sept. 1934
  - Borah for president, 1936 (by state)
    - Alabama-Idaho, (13 folders)
    - Idaho-Ohio, (24 folders) (Box 756)
    - Oklahoma-Wyoming, (13 folders) (Box 757)
  - Campaign of 1918
  - Campaign expenditures, 1924
    - Democratic, Socialist, and Progressive contribution record
    - Democratic state chairman
      - Dec. 1924-Jan. 1925, (2 folders)
      - Jan.-Feb. 1925 (Box 758)
    - Miscellaneous, Dec. 1924-Jan. 1925, undated
    - Progressive State Chairman, Dec.-Jan. 1925, (2 folders)
    - Republican contribution record
    - Republican refunds to states
    - Republican state chairman, Nov. 1924-Feb. 1925, (3 folders) (Box 759)
    - Socialist Party State chairman, Dec. 1924-Jan. 1925
  - Canadian treaty, Jan. 1925
  - "Cash and Carry," 1939, undated
  - Child Labor Amendment, Mar. 1937
  - Chile, proposed treaty, Feb.-Dec. 1928
  - China, May 1928
  - Claims, 1920-1933, (4 folders) (Box 760)
  - Commission on the purchase of embassy, legation, and consular buildings and grounds, 1923-1931
  - Cuba
    - 1905-1927
    - 1928-1929, (2 folders) (Box 761)
  - Cuba matters, Shipstead Committee, 1923-1929
  - Currency and money question, Dec 1933-Nov. 1934, (3 folders)
  - Debt cancellations, 1931
  - Education department, 1922-1927, undated, (2 folders) (Box 762)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, Feb.-Apr. 1938, (2 folders)
  - Fair Labor Standards Act, 1939
  - Farm matters, 1931-1937
  - Farm problems, 1935-1936
  - Foreign affairs
    - Letter to students of St. Olaf College, Northfield, Minn., Apr. 1939, (1 folder) (Box 763)
    - Reaction to speech, Mar.-Apr. 1938, (2 folders)
  - Foreign debt, Nov. 1932
  - Foreign defense expenditures, 1931-32
  - Foreign relations
    - Miscellaneous
      - Dec. 1923-Dec. 1925, (2 folders)
      - Jan. 1926-Dec. 1929, (6 folders) (Box 764)
      - Jan. 1930-1939, undated, (3 folders) (Box 765)
    - Panama Canal, 1933-35
  - French loan, Sept. 1927
  - German-Austrian decision, comment of the press, 1931
  - Gillette Resolution, Mar.-Apr. 1928
  - Gorgas Memorial Laboratory, Apr. 928
  - Great Britain, 1919-1930
  - Great Lakes, St. Lawrence Deep Waterway Treaty
    - 1927-1932
    - Oct. 1932-Feb. 1933, (2 folders) (Box 766)
  - Hungry, 1938
  - Imbrie matters, 1926-1928
  - Injunctions, use and abuse of, circa 1927
  - Isle of Pines, 1905
  - Item veto, 1936
  - Japanese treaty, 1939-1940
  - Jewish refugees and immigration laws
    - Nov. 1938, (4 folders)
    - Dec. 1938 (Box 767)
  - Judicial system
  - Kellogg-Briand Pact, Dec 1927-Dec. 1928
  - League of Nations, 1919-1921
    - Alabama
    - Arkansas
    - California
    - Colorado
    - Connecticut
    - District of Columbia
    - Egypt
    - Florida
    - France
    - Georgia
    - Hawaii
    - Idaho, (2 folders); (4 folders) (Box 768)
    - Idaho
      - Babb, James E., Jan.-Nov. 1919
      - Rockwell, Irvin E., Feb-Nov. 1919
    - Illinois
    - Indiana
    - Iowa
    - Ireland
    - Kansas
    - Kentucky
    - Maine
    - Maryland
    - Massachusetts (Box 769)
    - Massachusetts, Albert J. Beveridge, Jan. 1919-Sept. 1920
    - Michigan
    - Minnesota
    - Miscellaneous
    - Mississippi
    - Missouri
    - Montana
    - Nebraska
    - New Hampshire
    - New Jersey
    - New Mexico
    - New York City, (4 folders); (1 folder) (Box 770)
    - New York City, Frank A. Munsey, Feb.-Dec. 1919
    - New York
    - North Carolina
    - North Dakota
    - Oklahoma
    - Oregon
    - Overseas
    - Pennsylvania
    - Rhode Island
    - Shantung, China
    - South America
    - South Carolina
    - South Dakota
    - Tennessee
    - Texas
    - Utah
    - Vermont
    - Virginia
    - Washington
    - Wisconsin
  - Legislation, O'Mahoney-Borah bill (Box 771)
    - Jan.-July 1938, (7 folders)
    - Oct. 1938-Apr 1939 (Box 772)
  - Mellon, Andrew W., 1929
  - Monopoly and trade restraint
    - Jan.-Dec. 1938, (5 folders)
    - Jan.-Dec. 1939, undated, (6 folders) (Box 773)
  - Monroe Doctrine, 1928 (Box 774)
  - Naval appropriations, Mar. 1938
  - Negroes and the 1936 primary
  - Neutrality
  - Neutrality Act, repeal of, July-Sept. 1939, (2 folders)
  - New Deal